alliedmarketresearch.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Allied Market Research is committed to protecting client’s personal information and credentials. With due regard, the company introduces new and updated policy statements occasionally as and when new products & services are developed and new technologies are deployed. On 25th May 2018, the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) launched by EU replaced the existing 1995 European Data Protection Directive. Owing to advancements in digital era and the introduction of GDPR, we have come up with a more comprehensive version of our privacy laws, modernized to resonate with today’s fast-paced data-driven world.

Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy explains Allied Market Research’s (we, us, or our) strategic approach toward the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of the users’ information by the company. It summarizes the various ways we acquire and treat your Data when you access, visit, and/or use the Service. It also governs your Data that we may acquire offline. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected on sites, applications, destinations, or services linked to from the Service that we do not own or control.

**Collection and Use of Information**

Allied Market Research is involved in the process of assessing the viability of new goods or services through research conducted directly with the consumer. This practice allows our customers to discover the target market and record opinions and other inputs from consumers regarding interest in the product. The company collects quantitative market data through research and interviews, and thus, the data may fluctuate due to changes in market dynamics. It is not responsible for any false or misleading information provided by users or manufacturers.

Other data that we collect is extensively, but not limited to, your basic, personal, and navigational information. When you register for our services or newsletters, you are requested to provide your personal information, such as name, email, and contact details. This information is stored temporarily with your consent to improve the website–user experience. Also, when you purchase any entity through our website, the required credentials will be stored on the secure servers and systems owned and managed by Allied Market Research.

**Information Collected by Automated Means**

We might automatically collect some of your information as you navigate through our website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, unique browser identifiers, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities (traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data) over time and across third-party websites or other online services (i.e., behavioral tracking). This information helps us improve our website and deliver a better and more personalized service.

**Cookie Policy**

A cookie is a text file that a web browser will store on your machine with your permission. It helps analyze the web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. We use cookies to administer the website, store visitor preferences, record session information, which helps us improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users.

A cookie does not necessarily give us any access to your personal files over your computer or any information other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies by choosing the viable option in the dialog box that appears when you visit a website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Based on the data acquired from cookies, we are able to direct our visitors to new areas that they might be interested in. It also helps us customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and we take care that a user is not sent the same banner ad repeatedly.

**Compliance to Privacy Laws**

Allied Market Research is committed to respecting the users’ right to confidentiality. We abide by all the current government laws and regulations and recognize our obligations in continuously updating and expanding our measures to keep-up with the requirements of the newly introduced GDPR. You can read about our GDPR compliance [here](https://www.bigmarketresearch.com/gdpr-policy).

We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage, and disclosure of personal information (including sensitive personal information).

**Disclaimer**

The company takes utmost care to ensure that the information provided on the website is relevant and accurate. However, it does not provide any warranty, undertakings, or representations about the authenticity of the content on the website. It takes no responsibility if the client suffers any loss or damage due to the usage of the information on the website.

The company’s website includes certain links that will take you to third-party websites. However, it is not responsible and administers no control over the content on the websites. Such links are for general purposes only and do not endorse any material on these websites or any association with their operators. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

**Copyright Notice**

The content on the company’s website is copyright – Allied Market Research all rights reserved.

The client may print or download extracts from the website for personal use only. Apart from subsequent viewing purposes and personal use, they should not make use of any of the material stored on any medium.

Any resale, disclosure, lending, or reproduction of service or publication can only be made with the prior written permission from Allied Market Research.

Transmission and/or reproduction of any part from the website, by any means or in any form (whether photocopying, mechanical, electronic, recording, or otherwise), are prohibited without prior written permission.

**Policy Changes**

The company may come up with a new and updated policy statement occasionally by posting a revised version of the statement on the website. Kindly refer to this page frequently to check for the policy amendments, if any.
